

# KATA SERFŐZŐ

# **Digital Designer**

#### PERSONAL DATA

- Budapest, Hungary
- +3670 6153393
- kata.serfozo@gmail.com
- Be www.behance.net/kataserfozo
- https://kataserfozo.github.io

## TOOLS OF CHOICE

### Designing

Adobe XD Balsamique Sketch AfterEffects Illustrator InDesign Photoshop Lightroom Lottie

## Cooperating

Figma InVision Miro

#### **Building**

html, css Wordpress Elementor

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Hungarian **English** Swedish German

#### **EXTRACURRICULAR**

- Volunteering as a Digital Designer for an NGO
- 6 months in New Zealand on a working holiday scheme
- 3 months experience as a barista in London
- Volunteering for 3 months in Portugal in a surf camp
- Working as a freelance photographer at weddings and events
- Experience in Studio Photography

I'm a digital designer in love with UI and motion design. Due to my diverse professional experience, I am able to adapt to different environments while adhering to professional integrity. Besides arts and creating, I love developing my skills, learning new tools and improving my design skillset, while making aesthetically pleasing and useful products and designs.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

10/2020- present

## **Digital Designer** kadasolutions GmbH, remote

- UX and UI design for mobile application
- creating websites for companies in Switzerland and Hungary
- Motion graphic design
- creating and conceptualising graphic design materials (online and offline)
- creating custom-made illustrations

01/2020- 04/2020 UI Designer

# Lendis, Berlin, Germany

- Collaborating with stakeholders over collecting requirements, creating user flows, wireframes and mockups for both customer facing applications and internal tools
- Collaborating with engineering department over executing the visual designs all the way from wireframes to final deliverables
- Establishing a company wide design system

# 09/2018- 04/2019 UI Design course CareerFoundry

- UI design for music, messaging, note-taking apps
- UX and UI design for cooking application for mobile and responsive design
- UI design for delivery application for iOS & Android Native app
- UI design for money saving responsive website

10/2017 - 3/2018

# Graphic and Web Design intern MediaSales, Budapest, Hungary

- Creating banners, website and mobile interface design
- Creating images and ads for social media and presentations
- Designing products for print

# 11/2013 - 12/2016 Finance Porfessional-Reporting Specialist British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

- Employee database design, maintenance and reporting in business objects application
- Testing corporate data warehouse of project and people management tool
- Advising and solving issues of users of a project and people management system

# **EDUCATION**

09/2018 - 04/2019 CareerFoundry, distance education **UI** Design

01/2010 - 06/2010 Rønde Højskole , Rønde, Denmark Arts, Project Management

09/2009 - 12/2013 Eötvös Loránd University, Budapest, Hungary BA, English and Scandinavian Studies